<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Football Club</string>

    <string-array name="club_name">
        <item>Barcelona FC</item>
        <item>Real Madrid FC</item>
        <item>Bayern Munchen FC</item>
        <item>Manchester United FC</item>
        <item>Manchester City FC</item>
        <item>Chelsea FC</item>
        <item>AC Milan FC</item>
        <item>Arsenal FC</item>
    </string-array>

    <array name="club_image">
        <item>@drawable/img_barca</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_madrid</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_bayern</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_mu</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_city</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_chelsea</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_acm</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_arsenal</item>
    </array>

    <string-array name="desc_club">
        <item> Barcelona FC known simply as Barcelona and colloquially as Barca, is a professional football club based in Barcelona, Catalunya, Spain.
        Founded in 1899 by a group of Swiss, English and Catalan footballers led by Joan Gamper </item>
        <item> Real Madrid FC, commonly known as Real Madrid, is a professional football club based in Madrid, Spain.
        Founded on 6 March 1902 as the Madrid Football Club, the club has traditionally worn a white home kit since inception </item>
        <item> Bayern Munchen commonly known as FC Bayern München, is a German sports club based in Munich, Bavaria (Bayern)
        FC Bayern was founded in 1900 by 11 football players, led by Franz John. </item>
        <item> Manchester United commonly known as Man. United or simply United, is a professional football club based in Old Trafford, Greater Manchester,
            England, that competes in the Premier League, the top flight of English football. Nicknamed "the Red Devils", the club was founded as Newton Heath LYR Football Club in 1878,
            changed its name to Manchester United in 1902 and moved to its current stadium, Old Trafford, in 1910. </item>
        <item> Manchester City also known simply as City or the Cityzens, is a football club based in east Manchester, England.
            Founded in 1880 as St. Mark's, it became Ardwick Association Football Club in 1887 and Manchester City in 1894. </item>
        <item> Chelsea is a professional football club in London, England, that competes in the Premier League. Founded in 1905, the club's home ground since then has been Stamford Bridge.
            Chelsea won the First Division title in 1955, followed by various cup competitions between 1965 and 1971 </item>
        <item> AC Milan commonly referred to as A.C. Milan or simply Milan, is a professional football club in Milan, Italy, founded in 1899. The club has spent its entire history,
            with the exception of the 1980–81 and 1982–83 seasons, in the top flight of Italian football, known as Serie A since 1929–30. </item>
        <item> Arsenal is a professional football club based in Islington, London, England, that plays in the Premier League, the top flight of English football.
        Arsenal was the first club from the South of England to join The Football League, in 1893, and they reached the First Division in 1904. </item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
